Hello, okay, I'm not going to keep you guys waiting forever.
Mmm. Oh gosh, I'm all sore. I think I slept wrong. Oh
Anyway
It's inspired to talk about some people
Anybody you can give some suggestions about who you want to talk about
Because people like to talk about me or that people talk about me
In really bad ways
Hmm, I was just saying some unknown. Oh, it's not unknown, but you know, I'm too much. So let's just call her an anonymous person
That I have had a past friendship with
Oh God, it's just hey, what's up reasoning? Yeah reasoning is happy because there's not gonna be
Music right now. I don't know the first person. She says hi to me. It's first or hi to it's a person that is like, you know
Try to take down my channel for a long time. That's the first person she decides to say how I do the first person in her chat
You know also, it's Doc's turn, but
She's miss innocent she's miss oh, I don't know I don't know what's what's going on. I don't know what happened
No happen you can show you some what happened
You asked for it
See, what is it? It's gonna be a trip kick
God bless trip kick. Let me see. Oh my god
What this one
Typical psyche. Yeah, typical me
Typical Rob is always the pub bullshit. Okay
Anyway
A peace plan for Gaza
For the plan to advance Hamas must disarm
If you're over 50 and flying anywhere this holiday season you need to hear this
What do you think about, what do you think about, what do you think about that cage?
Are you going to still sit there in your la-la-lan thinking that guy wants you?
You desperate ass fucking fat hog.
Huh?
Barry doesn't jerk off to you. He jerks off to my titty pictures. I got proof of that
See the little bit more Kate and every time you post more pictures about me the more you incriminate yourself you fucking retard
Keep doing it waiting
Go live you emergency fat hog
You fucking disgusting bitch punch in the air
Are you so mad that Barry jerked off to my titties?
Ooh, oopsie, oopsie.
You thirsty, ugly, disgusting, jealous, no life, no good,
bad mother, no good role model bitch, doxing, fucking hog.
Fuck you.
I will fuck your whole fucking life up over and over again.
Yes.
Get the fuck out of my fucking chat.
You ever see me coming over in your chat?
You fucking ugly fucking fat hog.
I'm gonna put pictures of beta up there and think that I'm gonna fucking not like
You know fucking like literally on you what I'm gonna do. I'm gonna get a legal charge against you
I'm gonna make you cry at night
Barry would rather fuck me any day over you. I promise you that I promise you that you're
Fucking Kathy Bates for fucking misery you bet
You're miserable. You're miserable. You put cigarettes up your hoo-ha and you to get to the present system
All right, we're a man
How big is your koo-chee slot
Or
Scott
Talking all this shit that you talk about everybody else and you sit there acting like a fucking pit bull fuck you
What the fuck are you saying?
Hi.
How are you?
What do you care?
I care.
No you don't.
Thank you so much.
We had a bad...
We had a bad, a rough time, huh?
You never cared and you never will.
So why the fuck are you here?
I do care.
I know you're not, but you can, you know, you can come in, I'm sure you don't want to be on it, but you can come anytime.
You're always welcome.
Well, I can be back there.
Okay.
Let's see. I'll still come back here if you like, let me.
I worked through you fucking like playing clips of me and think I got a tattoo of some fucking stupid bitch on my fucking child.
You watched the whole thing, did you watch the whole thing I said or did you see that one sentence?
Are you letting people talk to my name and last name out there?
Letting them?
Not how much you care about me?
I can like do something about it, I can't.
But your name's out there anyway.
why do you have a show? You know what I would do? I did that there too, you know. I want to associate
myself with cowards. Well, you know, I know people at Brown Bird, everybody, I see you guys backstage.
I'm giving him the one-on-one, so he doesn't say we don't talk one-on-one. Okay, well, anyone wants to, you know.
you know if you don't believe me that there are people backstage I'll just tell you I know
just tell you there are 100 and good times okay well yeah I'm always lying right you're lying
I don't why I didn't ever call you like a liar or anything like like what are you like I mean
it's like you kind of think he said I had something to do with you getting stuff to your house
I did not say that but you I said you were honest. You said I laughed about it.
You were sitting on a panel with a guy that. You did. And you did too. I sat on a panel with them.
Yeah. Where? I'm also Tony.
Right. And Alex and all of
what we do. It's an open
to figure shit out. Did I
with that? Do you think I
to you? You're sitting th
with what he's saying. You
agree with my name on my
being dogs. Orange County
It's only one county well, yeah, I know I'm not a poon addict. I don't hate black people
I didn't fucking like what do you you just sitting there and you're like upset about
Two things and my last name is being exposed
What you know how many times are you gonna play cliff of me and crystalline?
Crystal and yeah
Why why did you do that just one day because I just found it that day and it was like why'd you find that?
Do I go looking for your fucking shit? I find it. Well, you know, well, you know, I have no idea
But you know what I don't maybe I don't think you would that's how much you fucking along me, right?
That's what people do, right
Well, I don't want to fight with people like that I only want people around me who actually give a fucking appreciate me
I do, but look, the people around you are kind of scared.
I think that some people are not really that great of people.
What you fucking did was you played Crisco fucking Anne,
where she had nothing to do with this community anymore.
I know.
Why?
Why'd you do that?
Why did I do that?
Because I just found something in it.
Why'd you go finding that?
Why did you go finding that?
Do you know me and her are cool?
We're friends?
I saw something else.
I'm thinking go ahead and go play it on your panel
Go play it. Do you see me playing that about you? I
Don't have that about me. I
I was involved in the car
Chanel and whether you were in your other people whether people judge you or not
You think this is the moment for me to fucking kick you
That's why you want
Fucking dogs to you. I never sent anything to your house. I never did all the fucking
Everything that happened to you happened to me too, but I'm still not going and digging about you
Like what like what did I say?
room and like you were screaming about oh i know tarot better than you now and then you
started like you were just trying to do something like really and still screaming on me and then
i got to find that that's terrible that's the worst thing i have done to you hey this is petty
shit like you know it's like it's like not even like that like bad is that worse on dogs and like
letting people like i don't know why you're so mad at me i got like i get so mad at you
you know what I am about you is the subpoena I don't hate you I will always love you and
you know what my last thing that I wrote on my community post was about you I will love you from
afar okay oh so that was the last thing she wrote right about me the next day she claims it was
about her ex boyfriend or something like that and I was crazy and I was like
Oh, I'm saying that she's in love with me, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah,
I think it's here.
Love for you is a bittersweet refrain.
This is the poem she wrote.
A melody that echoes a heart in pain.
Though we may be apart, you're always on my mind.
Wishing you
in the silence I'll hold on to the past and cherish it
I'll love you every day.
Aw, wouldn't that be a nice poem to receive from somebody?
And then they say it's not about you.
They say, why would you even think that?
You could say, that was about me.
She'll love me from afar, right?
What kind of person would do that and then say,
oh, well, that wasn't about you.
She said it was about me.
I don't know.
It's weird, huh?
One guess.
You guys want to come up? I'm not feeling really I can barely move right now. I really can't I'm like very very sore
Feel like I've been like hit by a truck actually
But I'm gonna come on I just wanted to play that little clip. Oh god, okay
Anyway
That's called like gaslighting, you know when you're like you say something and then you're like, oh, well, that's not true
And you just said it that's called gas
You can see I'm like my neck is like I can't I can't barely move. What's that bake lips?
I feel like I got hit by a truck my man. I think I slept wrong my neck. It's like in pain
So here I'm under the blanket keep the sun on me. Yeah, it's coming through a little bit to the curtains
I feel like I've been hit by a dump truck
You know it'll dump truck. Hey big clips. How are you doing today?
Hi, man. Anyway, I don't want to harp on it. It's just like it's just it keeps annoying me
She keeps going on like thing. Oh, I'm like some fucked-up person like some bad bad guy. I
Don't think I do anything. I never got it. I was vaccinated, but I never got it
I never got it. Everybody else like not pretty much got it. I
Just got two two shots
I think it was like the third shot that fucked everybody up, you know
I think the first two were like placebo's personally, but
You got it. Yeah, well, I believe it was a real thing
But I don't know what they put in all these booster shots and stuff
Just seems like a lot of people are affected in a negative way
By those but I don't know it. I don't want to get into medical
Medical stuff too bad. It was awful. I'm sorry. Did you lose your sense of taste?
I know a lot of people couldn't taste good to take some massive red pill capsules
For it. They were like six hours. Hey guys. Hey guys
So I'm just feeling not very good
Then I like I went to like the hero if she was and she's not talking about me
But everything is biscuit biscuit biscuit, you know
Hopefully the
I'll just do one more petty thing and then I'll probably like let you go because I can't really move right now
I don't know why
Yeah, I might be just sad a little bit a little bit sad
I'll be okay. I've been sadder
you're still sitting in the cage
talk tough online but the flavor don't last
snap like a cracker when the panel talks fast
hook, beaters, biscuits, dry and blend
no butter, no jam, just dust in your hand
claim you bring spice but you bring in regret
panel got receipts, we ain't finished yet
you came to the kitchen but forgot the recipe
serving up crumbs while I feast on
The smoke that won't stick your dough don't rise cuz you're game too quick
Just
Panel got receipts we ain't finished yet
Panel verse feast we don't starve on lies your plate got nothing
I don't like that you're the snack that everyone already four guys
Biscuits left on the shelf try to serve shade, but you played yourself
Penelites on true sharp like a knife biscuits crumble welcome to real life
but you're bringing regret panel got receipts we finished yet to the kitchen
but forgot the recipe serving up crumbs while I feast on legacy fire in the
oven you to smoke that won't be spanking you don't don't rise cuz your game too
quick
dry and bland no butter no jam just dust in the hand clean you bring spice but
you bring in regret panel got receipts we ain't finished yet
Okay, that's I mean, it's like I don't like it doesn't even like whatever anymore
Whatever's
Am I doing it not very good. I'm just like it. I'm in pain. I
like my
Neck is extremely sore I slept the wrong way my back feels like it got stepped on by a
300 pound
person
Um, I don't know and I had I'm having like bad dreams and stuff
um
And then I just want to sleep
I just want to sleep and then I can't fall asleep. It's okay. I'll be okay
I'll be okay. I just wish I could like run a show
Where the dreams about like there's a lot of dreams where it's like I'm like
My car is going up the bridge and I'm in the water and I like have to swim and I'm drowning and
Oh, it's was another one
Uh, just like bad things happening and
I'm sorry, I know it's hard to describe for you sometimes. Um being lost nightmares. Yeah
I'm just so sore my neck is just so sore right now. I
Wish I could stay on longer
But I'm sorry guys. I'm gonna try to come back on later if I feel better. I'm just gonna try to like lay down and like
Cover a little bit. I'm sorry. I love you guys. Have a good day. Okay. I'll be back